Bless His name as our spirits, souls, hearts cry, "Abba Father".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Our spirits and our souls cry out naturally, "Abba Father".
These are the words that resound in our hearts -
the words spoken by a Prophet - T.B. Joshua.
Say, "Lord, it is our prayer this morning.
Lord, take our hearts away from any fleshly desires
as our souls, our spirits cry out naturally, 'Abba Father'".
Come on. Bless His name as we worship.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Your Spirit in my heart cries naturally
Abba Father
Take my heart away from fleshly desires
Your Spirit in my heart cries naturally
Abba Father
Take my heart away from fleshly desires
Your Spirit in my heart cries naturally
Abba Father
Take my heart away from fleshly desires
Your Spirit in my heart cries naturally
Abba Father
Take my heart away from fleshly desires
Your Spirit in my heart cries naturally
Abba Father
Take my heart away from fleshly desires
Your Spirit in my heart cries naturally
Abba Father
Take my heart away from fleshly desires
As we sing this song, open up your mouth and say this prayer because the presence of God is here
and He hears every voice, every language.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
God's Spirit in our hearts cries naturally
Abba Father
Take our hearts away from fleshly desires
God's Spirit in our hearts cries naturally
Abba Father
Take our hearts away from fleshly desires
Come on. Bless the name of Jesus!
Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Say, "Lord, thank You for taking away every fleshly desire
because our hearts seek to follow You".
TT: Mel Flowers 24/12/2018
RV: ROBERT BEGIER 02/01/2019